A Guide to the Addison D. Campbell papers, 1948-1994
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Virginia State Democratic Party papers, 1967-1992., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 13-16)
  - Convention, 1976, delegates (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Convention, 1976, delegate credentials (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Convention, 1976, declarations of commitment (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Convention, 1976, certifications (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Convention, 1976, maps, booklets, ribbons, etc. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Convention, 1976, papers (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Convention, 1978, Henrico delegates (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (416-750, incomplete) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (752-822, incomplete) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1001-1049, incomplete) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1051-1100, incomplete) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1101-1150, incomplete) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1151-1200, incomplete) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1201-1234, incomplete) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1301-1355, incomplete) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1501-1600, incomplete) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Convention, 1978, certification (1601-1624, incomplete; no number; blank forms) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Convention, 1978, ballots for senator (Clive DuVal, Andrew Miller) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Convention, 1978, ballots for senator (Conoly Phillips, Rufus Phillips, Carrington Williams) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Convention, 1978, papers (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Convention, 1980, plan and call (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Convention, 1980, papers (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Convention, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Convention, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Convention, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, March-December 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Party plans, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Party plans, 1972, related papers (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1973, related papers (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1974, related papers (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Party plans, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Party plans, 1975, related papers (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Party plans, organization plans, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Party plans, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Party plans, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Party plans, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Party plans, no date (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - General papers, 1971-1974, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - General papers, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - General papers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General papers, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - General papers, no date (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local committees--Richmond-Henrico Committee, 1967-1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local committees--Richmond City Democratic Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local committees--Richmond City Democratic Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local committees--Chesterfield County Democratic Committee, 1972-1979, no date (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Local committees--Richmond Area Democratic Council, 1966, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Local committees--Charles City County Democratic Committee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Local committees--Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 1977, no date (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Local committees--Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Local committees--Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Local committees--Norfolk Democratic Committee, no date (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Local committees--Association of City and County Democratic Committee Chairmen, 1979, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Richmond Area Young Democrats papers, 1971-1980., Extent: 1 box. (Box 16)
  Richmond Area Young Democrats papers, 1971-1980, containing papers relating to the organization and operation of the Richmond area Young Democrats. Papers contain constitutions, correspondence, forms, invitations, memorandums, newsletters, notes, programs, resolutions, and other papers.
  - Papers, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Papers, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Papers, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Papers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Papers, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Papers, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Papers, no date (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Series V: Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner papers, 1973-1979, 1984., Extent: 1 box. (Box 16)
  Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner papers, 1973-1984, consisting of papers relating to the annual Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner held by the Virginia State Democratic Party, including remarks by President Jimmy Carter at the 1979 dinner. Papers include announcements, correspondence, invitations, programs, and other papers.
  - Papers, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Papers, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Papers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Series VI: National Democratic Party papers, 1964-1984., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 16-17)
  National Democratic Party papers, 1964-1984, containing papers relating to the organization and operation of the Democratic National Party, including its commissions, conventions and conferences. Papers contain amendments, badges, brochures, correspondence, charters, drafts, invitations, lists, manuals, memorandums, notes, pamphlets, plans, reports, rosters, tickets, and other papers.
  - Official manual for the Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Commission on Party Structure and Delegate Selection, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Democratic Charter Commission papers, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, Permanent Role [sic] of Delegates and Alternates (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, supplement list of certified delegates and alternates (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, draft charter and amendments (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, minority reports and petitions (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, charter draft and notes (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, correspondence, notes, etc. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, pamphlets (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - National Democratic Conference, 1974, brochures, tickets, ephemera (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - National convention, 1976, booklets (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - National convention, 1976, review of the 1976 delegate selection experience (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - General papers, 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - General papers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - General papers, 1976, booklets (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General papers, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - General papers, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General papers, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Series VII: VEA/NEA records, 1972-1992., Extent: 2. (Box 18-19)
  VEA/NEA records, 1972-1992, consisting of papers regarding the Virginia Education Association and the National Education Association and their efforts to campaign for and elect candidates the organizations believed would benefit teachers and the education system. Includes papers regarding the VEA's Practical Pragmatic Politics Workshop and Leadership Development Academy. Papers contain agendas, booklets, clippings, correspondence, forms, guides, maps, memorandums, newsletters, notes, reports, surveys, workbooks, and other papers.
  - Virginia Education Association--Practical Pragmatic Politics Workshop, [1972-1973?] (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Education Association--Practical Pragmatic Politics Workshop, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Education Association--VEA Political Action seminar, Leadership Development Academy, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Education Association--Key People in Virginia Government, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Education Association--Legislative News Flash, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Education Association--Research Service, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Education Association--VEA News, 1975, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Education Association--Virginia Journal of Education, March 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1974 (folder 1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1974 (folder 2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1974 (folder 3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1975, clippings (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Education Association--general papers, 1978-1979, 1982, no date (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Local education associations papers, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - National Education Association--The Political Charette (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - National Education Association--Political Persuasion Verbal Skills Workbook (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Direct Mail Campaigning (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Door-to-Door Campaigning (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Organizing a Volunteer Campaign (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Political Action Among Teachers (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Targeting (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - National Education Association--NEA Political Action Series: Telephone Campaigning (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - National Education Association--NEA Advocate, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - National Education Association--NEA Reporter, 1974, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - National Education Association--general papers, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - National Education Association--general papers, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Virginia State Board of Elections papers, 1971-1980., Extent: 1 box. (Box 19)
  Virginia State Board of Elections papers, 1971-1980, containing papers regarding the legal process of elections in Virginia. Papers include calendars, correspondence, legislation, lists, pamphlets, reports, and other papers.
  - Papers, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Papers, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Papers, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Series IX: Elections, 1965-1994., Extent: 4 boxes and 4 oversize folders. (Box 19-22)
  Elections, 1965-1994, consisting of papers relating to political campaigns for local, state, and national elections in Henrico County and Virginia. Papers contain advertisements, agendas, ballots, brochures, calendars, circulars, clippings, correspondence, handbills, lists, newsletters, notes, press releases, and other papers.
  - Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Papers, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Candidates' correspondence, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Campaign literature, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Robison James campaign for House of Delegates, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Papers, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Candidates' literature and papers (Henrico County), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Robison James campaign for House of Delegates, 1975 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Robison James campaign for House of Delegates, 1975 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Joint Democratic campaign in Henrico County, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Candidates' literature (non-Henrico County), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bud Zumwalt U.S. Senate campaign, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bud Zumwalt U.S. Senate campaign, Project 2000, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Presidential election--Democratic primary/pre-convention (Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Presidential election--Democratic primary/pre-convention (Lloyd Bentsen, Edmund Pat Brown, Henry M. Jackson, Sargent Shriver, Morris Mo Udall), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Presidential election, 1976, general campaign (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Papers, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Statewide offices (Governor, Lieutenant-Governor, Attorney-General)--Democratic Rainbow ticket (Henry Howell, Chuck Robb, Ed Lane), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Governor--Democratic primary and general election (Henry Howell), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Governor--Democratic primary (Andrew Miller), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Governor--general election (John N. Dalton, Republican candidate), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lieutenant governor--Democratic primary and general election (Chuck Robb) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Lieutenant governor--Democratic primary (Ira Lechner), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lieutenant governor--Democratic primary (Major Reynolds), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Attorney General--Democratic primary and general election (Ed Lane), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Attorney General--Democratic primary (John T. Schell), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General--Democratic primary (Erwin Shad Solomon, John L. Melnick), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - House of Delegates (Robert Bob Ball, Benjamin Lambert), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - House of Delegates (Robison Rob James, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Henrico County Commonwealth's Attorney (Rod Chapman, James Kulp), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Richmond City Council (Henry Marsh, III), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Papers, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention and general election (Andrew Miller), 1978 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention and general election (Andrew Miller), 1978 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Hunter Andrews), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Fred Babson), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Flora Crater), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Clive DuVal), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Conoly Phillips), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Rufus Phillips), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Senate--Democratic convention (Carrington Williams), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Congress (Lew Puller), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Papers, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Papers, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Governor--general election (Chuck Robb), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Lieutenant Governor, Attorney General--general election (Richard Davis, Gerald Baliles), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Lieutenant Governor, Attorney General--Democratic primary (Ira Lechner, Erwin Shad Solomon), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lieutenant Governor, Attorney General--general election (Nathan Miller, Wyatt Durrette, Republican candidates), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - House of Delegates (Robert Bob Ball, Robison Rob James), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - House of Delegates (Jim Gilmore, Walter Stosch, Republican candidates), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Papers, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Papers, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Papers, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Papers, 1992 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Papers, 1992 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Papers, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Papers, no date (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Election posters--Armistead Booth for U.S. Senate; William Spong for U.S. Senate; Joe Fisher for U.S. Senate; Chuck Robb for U.S. Senate, 1966, 1972, 197?, 1994 (Folder oversize 1)
  - Election posters--Andy Miller for Attorney General; John L. Melnick for Attorney General; Ira Lechner for Lieutenant Governor; Axselle, Ball, Jame, and Reid for House of Delegates, 1973, 1977, no date (Folder oversize 2)
  - Election posters--Chuck Robb for Governor; Terry/Beyer/Dolan for Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General; America's Message for Congress, 1981, 1993, no date (Folder oversize 3)
  - Election posters--Carter/Mondale for President/Vice President; Walter Mondale for President; Clinton/Gore for President/Vice President; University of Richmond Presidential Debate, 1976, 1984, 1992 (Folder oversize 4)
- Series X: Election Returns, 1948-1981., Extent: 1 box. (Box 22)
  Election Returns, 1948-1981, containing the returns of local and state elections in Henrico County, Virginia. Papers consist of clippings, returns, and other papers.
  - Returns, 1948-1960 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Returns, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Returns, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Returns, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Returns, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Returns, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Returns, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Returns, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Returns, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Returns, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Returns, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Returns, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Returns, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Returns--Henrico County precincts (Bethlehem-Derbyshire), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Returns--Henrico County precincts (Eanes-Highland Gardens), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Returns--Henrico County precincts (Highland Springs-Montrose), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Returns--Henrico County precincts (Monument Hills-Spottswood), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Returns--Henrico County precincts (Sullivans-Wistar), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Returns--Henrico County, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Returns, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Series XI: General Politics papers, 1963-1993., Extent: 9 boxes and 3 oversize folders. (Box 22-31)
  General Politics papers, 1963-1993, consisting of papers relating to women in politics, collective bargaining and unions, the Virginia general assembly, precints and polling sites, voters, inaugurations, political organizations, and other general aspects of political campaigns and actions. Papers include ballots, campaign buttons, correspondence, clippings, directories, ephemera, guides, essays, eulogies, forms, invitations, legislation, lists, maps of Henrico County precincts, memorandums, magazines, minutes, newsletters, notes, plans, poll books, posters, publications, reports, rolls, and other papers.
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, February-August 1973 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1973 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1979, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, March-April 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, May 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, June 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, July-November 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1975 (multiple dates, no dates) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1977, 1979, no date (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Henrico County Registrar's Office papers, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Richmond Area Voter Registration Coordinating Committee papers, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Redistricting plans, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Precincts, district maps, sample ballots, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Election day instructions and poll workers, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Election laws, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Spottswood precinct, Tuckahoe district, poll books, 14 June 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Proposed voting precincts, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Polling and campaigning, no date (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Women in politics, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Women in politics, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Women in politics, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Women in politics, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Richmond Area Democratic Woman's Club papers, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Public employee bargaining, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Unions, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Democratic party (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Republican party (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - John F. Kennedy eulogies, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ralph Nader (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Federal Election Commission papers, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Ethics of Politics, Robison James, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Gubernatorial inaugurations, 1974, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Presidential inauguration, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Papers relating to the General Assembly, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - General papers, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - General papers, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - General papers, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - General papers, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - General papers, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - General papers, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - General papers, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - General papers, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - General papers, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - General papers, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - General papers, 1993, no date (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Axselle Action, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Organization Second & Eighth Congressional Districts of Virginia, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Democrat, 1974, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1977, 1982, DuVal's Daily (1977); Virginia Politics (1977); The Crusader Newsletter (1977); The Chesterfield Democrat (1977); In the Public Interest (1982); Virginians for Civic Responsibility (1982) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Addresses Home and Business Phones of Members of the General Assembly and President of the Senate, 1976 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly of Virginia List of Members and Districts, 1976 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly of Virginia Manual of the Senate and House of Delegates, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Democratic Party Plans, 1932 (and as amended) (Box 25)
  - Virginia Election Laws, 1975, 1978, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Your Virginia State Government, 1976 (Box 25)
  - The Constitution of the United States, Bicentennial edition (Box 25)
  - How Our Laws Are Made, 1976 (Box 25)
  - The Working Congress, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Ruminations on Reason and Law: a Spong Song, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Projections and Economic Base Analysis: Richmond Metropolitan Area, 1972 (Box 25)
  - The Capitol: A Pictorial History (Box 25)